let's see nimu has come back crazier than ever
a ver nimu ha vuelto más loca que nunca
This is
Esto es
like this nimu has come back crazier than ever or
así nimu ha vuelto más loca que nunca o
what nimu has gone crazy eh nimu has
qué nimu ha vuelto loquísima eh nimu ha
gone crazy the other day nimu
vuelto loquísima el otro día nimu le
hit the cool Alex Well, let
pegó una [__] a al Alex molón Le pó
's say he slapped him so hard that he left him
vamos le pegó un guantazo que lo dejó
shaking eh the other one didn't respond or
temblando eh el otro ni ha respondido ni
say anything let's say he was trying to be
ha dicho nada vamos ha intentaba serc
like nimu's T didn't exist but
como si no existiera el T de nimu pero
BS basically nimu slapped this
BS básicamente nimu le metió un guantazo
cool Alex who was
al Alex molón este no que estaba
promoting his rewi and all this [ __ ]
promocionando su rewi y tod esta movida
and nimu told him the truth he didn't tell him Hey
y nimu le dijo una verdad no le dijo Oye
something that Javi oliveira has been saying for I do
algo que Javi oliveira lleva diciendo ya
n't know how long no Hey, it
no sé cuánto tiempo no Oye que es que
turns out that you say that you do a
resulta que que tú dices que haces un
rewind that represents the community but it
rewind que representa la comunidad pero
doesn't represent the community it's a rewind
no representa la comunidad es un rewind
of well you and your people, of your
de bueno tuyo y de tu gente de tus
friends no And of your idols because
amigos no Y de tus ídolos porque al
in the end Alex cool is still a fan of gref, of gref Okay and now it seems that she was in revolt on Twitter that she was in revolt on Twitter
que estaba revuelta en Twitter por
because there are  someone who won't stop taking out
porque hay alguien que no para de sacar
Well I think this is a bit
Bueno yo creo que esto es un poco en
general I think this is a bit
general yo creo que esto es un poco
general it doesn't say luar I don't know who he's
general no dice luar no sé de quién
talking about but the videos with the most likes about
habla pero los vídeos con más lik sobre
her in the last few days have them
ella en los últimos días los tienen
outer Play and youtuber gossip in a
outer Play y chisme youtubero en una
response he left Of course it's someone who
respuesta dejó Claro que es alguien que
receives a lot of likes so it's most
recibe muchos likes por lo que lo más
likely that he is a
probable es que sea un
youtuber someone who receives a lot of likes
youtuber alguien que recibe muchos likes
But I don't understand the point let's see let's see
Pero no entiendo el punto a ver a ver
wait it's that I can't see it because he
espérate es que no lo puedo ver porque
has a blog let's see if nimu nimu didn't
me tiene blog a ver si nimu nimu no me
take my
quitó el
blog nimun didn't take my blog and I don't know
blog nimun no me quitó el blog y no sé a
what he means by this look
qué se refiere lugar con esto mira dice
the tweet says months ago I stopped
el tweet hace meses que dejé de hacer
streaming and there are people who continue Breaking my
Stream y hay gente que sigue Rompiendo
balls and talking about me Hahaha I guess they
las bolas y hablando de mí Jajaja supen
seem like my
me parecen mis
exes of course she could be saying this
ex claro esto lo puede estar diciendo
about a youtuber or not I mean I don't think she
por un youtuber o no O sea yo no creo
's saying it Or yes let's see she could
que lo esté diciendo O sí a ver podría
be saying it about a youtuber because they
estar diciéndolo por un youtuber porque
make videos of her okay it sounds familiar to me I have
se hagan vídeos de ella vale me suena yo
n't made any nimu videos
no he hecho ningún vídeo de nimu
lately it could be because of videos from the
últimamente podría ser por vídeos de la
criminal complaint that a few days ago
denuncia penal que hace unos días
also but that was a while ago
también pero eso ya hace más tiempo
This one I don't know what
Este no sé de lo que va
world is about Well this one will go on about the subject of on
mundo Bueno este ira sobre lo del tema
the subject of being cool and this one
de sobre el tema de al molón y este le
throws Juan and Ari you're good But they
tira Juan y Ari eres bueno Pero ellos
are bad you're good but I don't know it's been a
son malos eres bueno pero no sé no hace
while since I saw a video of
tiempo que no he visto ni un vídeo de de
nauter or or the gossip dude so
nauter ni de ni del chisme tío así que
no I don't know what it was about But I know that
no no lo sé de qué iba Pero yo sé que
we here have talked about the
nosotros aquí hemos hablado sobre el
issue of the criminal complaint what maybe we have
tema de la denuncia penal lo que a lo
n't put it in
mejor no la hemos puesto en
maybe we haven't put it in
a lo mejor no la hemos puesto en
thumbnail Lately I don't know the truth
miniatura Últimamente no lo sé la verdad
but it is that it can be referred to
pero es que se puede referir
perfectly
perfectamente
Ah well no because here
Ah pues no porque aquí lo está
your ex the minor or the
negando tu ex el menor de edad o el
manager who scammed with
manager que estafó con
3000 is denying it I'm not talking about bos the
3000 no estoy hablando de bos el
idiot who doesn't even informs and repeats
[__] que ni Se informa y repite
things that are not true to scratch like
cosas que no son verdad para rascar like
eh what can I tell you I mean it could be
eh qué te digo o sea podría estar
talking about any gossip channel
hablando de cualquier canal de salseo
that there is that we have talked about in
que haya que hayamos hablado de ella en
the last few days or about rups himself okay
los últimos días o del propio rups vale
rups himself who well keeps
el propio rups que bueno sigue dejando
dropping
cayendo
things keeps dropping things but doesn't
cosas sigue dejando caer cosas pero no
say anything Of course rup is putting like
dice nada Claro rup está poniendo como
tweet of well I'm glad
tweet de bueno me alegro
eh justice is being done No but
eh la justicia se está haciendo No pero
no I don't understand much what
no no entiendo mucho lo que está
rup is doing it's that I don't understand it let's see
haciendo rup es que no lo entiendo a ver
if he answers me because I spoke to him to
si me contesta porque le hablé para
ask him no because he is putting this
preguntarle no porque está poniendo es
tweet because they are tweets as if it
tweet porque son tweet como que da a
implies that something has happened but you don't
entender como que ha pasado algo pero no
say it it's like let's see if you are part
lo dices es como a ver si tú eres parte
of a procedure you can speak I
de un procedimiento tú puedes hablar O
mean nothing happens because you say I won I
sea no pasa nada porque digas he ganado
lost it is suspended or whatever
he perdido está suspendido o lo que sea
no Javi You said that n was with
no Javi Tú dijiste que n estaba con
delox dude you've swallowed TR hours of
delox tío te has tragado TR horas de
telesalseo and you were in the chat Toc I would
telesalseo y estabas en el chat Toc Me
love to see you Mauricio out of
encantaría verte Mauricio ya por
curiosity dude I mean because you've
curiosidad tío o sea porque te te has
spent three hours in tea salseo
pegado tres horas en tes salseo dándole
turning my words around to get on my
vuelta a mis palabras para tocar las
nerves no I don't know if at a joking level
narices no no sé si a nivel de broma
trolling or what And here the same thing I haven't
troleo o qué Y aquí lo mismo yo no he
said that nmo is with delox I
dicho que nmo esté con delox Yo lo
think it obviously I think it
pienso evidentemente yo lo pienso
obviously Of course I think it eh Let's
evidentemente Claro que lo pienso eh A
see but I think it and anyone who
ver pero lo pienso yo y cualquiera que
follows him on instagram but if so many
le siga en instagram pero si tantos dí
together the two of us traveling together eh  with his
junto los dos viajando juntos eh con la
girlfriend he's no longer there with his girlfriend he's
novia ya no está no con la novia ya no
no longer seen they've removed the photos they
no se le ve han quitado las fotos que
had together and I don't know what to see I think it's
tenían juntos y no sé qué a ver yo creo
obvious But what does that have to do
que es obvio Pero qué tiene que ver eso
with this tweet of
con con este tweet de
nimo what about Paula gonu is to flip out
nimo lo de Paula gonu es para flipar
now we'll see also what about Paula
ahora lo veremos también lo de Paula
onono which I don't know honestly eh nimu
onono que no lo sé la verdad eh nimu
based on the tweet from the other day but
basadisimo en el twit del otro día pero
in this one you've come across a little
en este te has quado un poco
weak in that same tweet from nimu a
flojilla en ese mismo tweet de nimu un
Dallas hater told nimu to
hater de Dallas le puso a nimu
eat the hate for selling out to
que se coma el hate por venderse a
Dallas my goodness I'm
Dallas madre mía estoy
checking that people are still
comprobando que la gente sigue
terrible Javi don't threaten him what to whom
fatal Javi no lo amenaces el qué a quién
Poor Mauricio No man leave him he's a
Al pobre Mauricio No hombre déjalo es un
loyal follower
seguidor fiel